<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Simurai</title>
    <link>http://github.com/kennethormandy/hb-simurai</link>
    <description>Simurai’s site as a Harp boilerplate.</description>
    <atom:link href="http://github.com/kennethormandy/hb-simurai/blog/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
       
    
       
        <item>
          <title>Start a blog with Harp</title>
          <description><![CDATA[<p>I’ve always enjoyed pretending to be a developer. Faking my way through new web technologies has become a familiar exercise. This time was different.</p>
<p>The deception didn’t come from me, but my own development environment. I was using preprocessors to translate markup and code into something more common. Preprocessors make HTML &amp; CSS much more capable.Repeatedly arranging them, however, didn’t make <em>me</em> feel more capable.</p>
<p>Still, they are so useful, I continued working however they demanded. As I understood it, continually compiling my preprocessed code down to HTML, CSS &amp; JavaScript was necessary for every project. I thought it was just how preprocessing worked—but it’s not.</p>
<p>This was in the back of my mind when I first tried <a href="http://harpjs.com">Harp</a>, the static web server with built-in preprocessing. Support for Markdown, Jade, LESS, Stylus, and more are all present. With Harp, the compiled HTML, CSS &amp; JavaScript files aren’t tossed back into my project—I don’t need them there. Instead, as I make changes, they are delivered where they actually need to be: the browser.</p>
<p><a href="http://kennethormandy.com/journal/start-a-blog-with-harp">Read the rest of the post on Kenneth’s site</a></p>
]]></description>
          <pubDate>Tue May 06 2014 19:00:00 GMT-0500 (CDT)</pubDate>
          <link>http://github.com/kennethormandy/hb-simurai/blog/[object Object]</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://github.com/kennethormandy/hb-simurai/blog/[object Object]</guid>
        </item>
      
    
       
        <item>
          <title>Run a Background Process on Linux</title>
          <description><![CDATA[<h1>Run a Process in the Background on Linux</h1><p>I bumped into this question while setting up Selenium on CentOS. Saving this for myself for future reference.</p>
<pre><code>nohup java -Dwebdriver.chrome.driver=chromedriver -jar selenium-server-standalone-2.53.0.jar &amp;
</code></pre><p>The importance is <code>nuhup</code> and <code>&amp;</code>.</p>
]]></description>
          <pubDate>Thu May 05 2016 19:00:00 GMT-0500 (CDT)</pubDate>
          <link>http://github.com/kennethormandy/hb-simurai/blog/[object Object]</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://github.com/kennethormandy/hb-simurai/blog/[object Object]</guid>
        </item>
      
    
       
        <item>
          <title>Heyooo</title>
          <description><![CDATA[<h1>Heyo</h1><p>Hi. Let’s make a simple blog with <a href="http://harpjs.com">Harp</a>.</p>
]]></description>
          <pubDate>Thu May 05 2016 19:00:00 GMT-0500 (CDT)</pubDate>
          <link>http://github.com/kennethormandy/hb-simurai/blog/[object Object]</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://github.com/kennethormandy/hb-simurai/blog/[object Object]</guid>
        </item>
      
    
  </channel>
</rss>
